

Contact

niklas.rotkonen@hotmail.com

0503561337

Helsinki

github.com/rotkonen

Linked in

Languages

Finnish Native

Swedish Native

English Proficient

Skills/Tools

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Angular, React, Vue.js

Node.js, MongoDB, NoSQL

Python, C++

Visual Studio Code, GitHub

Microsoft 365

Niklas Rötkönen

PROFILE

I have just graduated as an engineer in information and communication technology, with experience in providing technical support and working as a summer trainee in various IT roles within the industry. I have proficiency in both front-end and backend technologies. I possess strong problem-solving skills and have a keen desire to develop my expertise in various aspects of software development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CGI

Service Desk Specialist

9/2021 - 12/2021

 Providing technical support to end-users in various technical issues, including answering support questions and handling service requests.

Fortum

Summer trainee

5/2019 - 9/2019

 Software testing, maintenance of asset management system, as well as equipment installations, updates, maintenance, and user support.

Summer trainee

5/2018 - 9/2018

 RPA development, maintenance of asset management system, as well as equipment installations, updates, maintenance, and user support.

Summer trainee

5/2017 - 9/2017

• Process IT. Server maintenance. Computer-related problems.

EDUCATION

Metropolia University of Applied Sciences 30/6/2022-18/6/2024

Information Technology, Engineering Student

243/240 credits

Thesis: Angular basics online course for Metropolia University

Arcada University of Applied Sciences 2015-2021

Information Technology, Engineering Student